ο Θεός της ηχάριτης,
Κύριε Λέησον,
της Παναγίας Αχράτου,
υπερευλογημένης ενδόξου,
δεσποινήσιμον Θεοτόκου
και αϊπαρθένου Μαρίας,
μεταπάντων των Αγίων
γημονεύσαντες,
εαυτούς και αλλήλους
και πάσα την ζωήν ημών,
Χριστό το Θεό
παραθώμεθα.
Συγκύριε
Ο της Σοντοκράτος και σου έστειν η Βασιλεία και η δύναμης και η δόξα του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγίου Πνεύματος νυν και αη και εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν, ο Εύσχημον Ιωσήφ από του ξύλου καθελών του άχραντών σου σώμα.
Συνδώνει καθαρά η λύστας και αρώμασιν, ενήματι και νόκυδεύσας απέθετο,
αλλά τριήμερος ανέστης Κύριε παρέχον το κόσμο το μεγαέλαιο.
Δόξα Πατρή και Υωκή Αγιοπνεύματι τες μυροφόρης γυνέξη παρά το μνήμα επιστά.
The Lord has prepared his throne in the heavens, and his kingdom rules over all.
Through the intercessions of the Theodokos, Savior, and the Holy Spirit,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
A gift for the presents.
Presents.
Oh my goodness, we're giving presents now.
Wow.
And let's see.
What would you prefer?
What kind of present do you want for Christmas?
I don't know.
You don't know.
What do you want for Christmas?
A lapar.
A lot.
Top, you said?
What do you want?
You don't know.
What do you want for Christmas?
Well, you're going to buy presents for people.
What are you going to get for mom and dad?
Are you going to get mom, who's going to get mom
a $1 gift card at Starbucks?
No, you aren't.
Don't even tell me you are.
You know you're not going to do that.
What are you going to do?
For mom and dad, you're going to do something more
or from what you want.
have. All of us do that. We do that, we look at who the person is
and we will give something something, but it's with the
how much importance they are in our lives. That's how we end up doing that.
Okay? So do you want a one dollar Starbucks gift card? Would you prefer an
I'm an iPad.
Praise Him in the heart.
Metaphobus, theopisteus, chegapis, prosentete
With the fear of God, with faith, and with love drawn ears.
Thank you.
The Lord is the Son of God.